Register of the William T. Poole collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Un-American Activities Subject File, 1920-1976 (Box 51-231.)
  - California Democratic Council. Letter and resolution, 1962 (Folder 66: 7)
  - California Emergency Defense Committee. Bulletins, flyers, press releases, and pamphlet (The Truth Goes Marching On), 1951-1952 (Folder 66: 8)
  - California Labor School [San Francisco]. Schedule, clippings, and letters by Holland Roberts, 1951-1957 (Folder 66: 9)
  - California Legislative Conference. Almanac, reports, programs, flyers, circulated documents, clippings, and HUAC memorandum, 1947-1956 (Folder 66: 10-11)
  - Californians for Liberal Representation. Circular letter, flyer, and clipping, 1966 (Folder 66: 12)
  - Campaign End the Air War. Printed appeal, 1972 (Folder 67: 1)
  - Campus Concerned Democrats. Printed appeal by faculty members of various universities, 1968 (Folder 67: 2)
  - Carlson, Gregg. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 67: 3)
  - Carrie Chapman Catt Memorial Fund [League of Women Voters project]. Brochures and pamphlets (The Fourteenth Amendment and Civil Liberty; Freedom Agenda in the Community; Freedom of Speech and Press; How to Organize a Freedom Agenda Project; Is Politics Your Job?; Let's Talk about Liberty; The Role of Political Parties U.S.A.; Self-Government USA; Where Constitutional Liberty Came From), 1951-1957 (Folder 67: 4)
  - Case Western Reserve Medical Students for Peace in Vietnam. Petition, 1968 (Folder 67: 5)
  - Catholic Church. Correspondence, flyers, serial issue, journal articles, and clippings, 1965-1973. (Folder 67: 6)
    Includes letter by James E. Groppi, and HUAC reply to Catholic critics
  - Catholic Peace Fellowship. Printed article, 1966 (Folder 67: 7)
  - Catholic University Movement for Peace and Freedom in Vietnam. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 67: 8)
  - Catholic Worker. Flyers, serial issues (Catholic Worker), and pamphlets (Blessed Are the Peacemakers; Two Agitators: Peter Maurin, Ammon Hennacy), 1944-1966 (Folder 67: 9)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights [New York City]. Circular letters and brochures, 1971-1974 (Folder 67: 10)
  - Center for Cuban Studies [New York City]. Letter and leaflet, 1970 (Folder 67: 11)
  - Center for Marxist Education [New York City]. Schedules, brochures, circular letter, flyer, and clipping, 1969-1975 (Folder 67: 12)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions [Santa Barbara, California]. Circular letters, brochures, and journal article, 1966-1971 (Folder 67: 13)
  - Center for United Labor Action [New York City]. Letter, serial issues (United Labor Action), and pamphlets (The Blast Furnace Brothers; Welfare; Working Women), 1971-1975 (Folder 67: 14)
  - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors. Circular letters, flyers, program, and pamphlet (Handbook for Conscientious Objectors), 1965-1973 (Folder 67: 15)
  - Champion. Serial issues, 1937-1938 (Folder 67: 16)
  - Champion of Youth. Serial issues, 1936-1937 (Folder 67: 17)
  - Charter Group for a Pledge of Conscience. Letter, circulated documents, statement, and newsletters, 1965-1968 (Folder 68: 1)
  - Chemical and biological warfare protest (General). Circular letters, flyers, leaflets, journal articles, and Congressional speech, 1966-1967 (Folder 68: 2)
  - Cherpitel, Sidney. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 68: 3)
  - Chicago Action Community. Flyers re draft, 1969 (Folder 68: 4)
  - Chicago Area Committee to Defend All Political Prisoners. Flyers, 1973 (Folder 68: 5)
  - Chicago Area Council [re Vietnam War]. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 68: 6)
  - Chicago Area Draft Resisters [CADRE]. Circulated appeal and clippings, 1967-1968 (Folder 68: 7)
  - Chicago Committee for Spanish Freedom. Leaflet, 1946 (Folder 68: 8)
  - Chicago Committee to Defend the Bill of Rights. Letters, circulated documents, flyers, and clippings, 1961-1970 (Folder 68: 9)
  - Chicago Committee to End the War in Vietnam. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 68: 10)
  - Chicago Committee to Stop HUAC. Flyer, undated (Folder 68: 11)
  - Chicago Connections [re rights of prisoners]. Newsletters, 1971-1973 (Folder 68: 12)
  - Chicago Defense Committee [re Chicago 8]. Circular letters, 1970 (Folder 68: 13)
  - Chicago Legal Defense Committee. Newsletter, 1968 (Folder 68: 14)
  - Chicago Movement Nonviolent Training Center. Training manual and memorandum, 1971 (Folder 68: 15)
  - Chicago Peace Council. Letter, informant's report, Chicago Peace Council reports, flyers, circulated documents, and clippings, 1966-1973 (Folder 68: 16)
  - Chicago Star. Bulletin, 1940 (Folder 68: 17)
  - Chicago Women for Peace. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 68: 18)
  - Chicago Women's Committee to End the War in Vietnam. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 68: 19)
  - Chicago Workshop in Nonviolence. Minutes and circular letter, 1966 (Folder 68: 20)
  - Chicagoans for Freedom of Travel to Cuba. Pamphlet (New Cuba), 1964 (Folder 68: 21)
  - Children's Medical Relief International. Report re Vietnam, 1973 (Folder 68: 22)
  - Children's Peace Union. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 68: 23)
  - Chile. Flyers, leaflets, newsletters, and circulated documents issued by miscellaneous Chilean solidarity groups, Library of Congress Legislative Reference Service report on change of regime in Chile, and clippings, 1971-1974 (Folder 68: 24)
  - China (Folder 68)
    - Chinese government English-language issuances. Radio broadcast summaries, statement, and serial issues (Hsinhua Weekly; Peking Review), 1956-1974 (Folder 68: 25)
    - Chinese government English-language pamphlets (Chou En-lai on Present International Situation; A Comment on the March Moscow Meeting; The Electoral Law of the People's Republic of China; In Refutation of Modern Revisionism; Mao Tse-tung's Thought Is the Invincible Weapon; Support the People of Vietnam; "Theory" and Practice of the Modern Revisonists; Who Will Win in South Vietnam?), 1953-1968 (Folder 69: 1)
    - Material about China. Press releases, flyers, journal articles, Congressional speeches, clippings, and pamphlets (Exodus from China; Life in Mainland China Today; Mao: War or Peace?; The Press in China; Red China Speaks), 1949-1971 (Folder 69: 2)
  - Christianity and Crisis. Serial issue, reprint, and circular, 1969-1970 (Folder 69: 3)
  - Church of Scientology. Serial issues (Freedom Scientology), 1970 (Folder 69: 4)
  - Churchman. Serial issues, and bulletin, 1965-1973 (Folder 69: 5)
  - Churchmen to End the Draft in 1971. Flyers (Folder 69: 6)
  - Cinema Educational Guild. Report, 1961 (Folder 69: 7)
  - Citizen Exchange Corps [re exchange visits to Soviet Union]. Circulars and advertisement, 1966-1967 (Folder 69: 8)
  - Citizens' Campaign against Napalm. Letter, flyers, clipping, and pamphlet (Napalm: Made in U.S.A.), 1966 (Folder 69: 9)
  - Citizens Committee for Constitutional Liberties (Folder 69)
    - General. Letters, leaflets, flyers, and clippings, 1961-1969 (Folder 69: 10)
    - Liberty. Serial issues, 1965-1969 (Folder 69: 11)
    - Pamphlets (Concentration Camps U.S.A.; Voices for Liberty), 1964-1966 (Folder 70: 1)
  - Citizens Committee for Hal Levin for Congress [New York City]. Flyer, 1966 (Folder 70: 2)
  - Citizens Committee for Julian Bond. Printed appeal, 1966 (Folder 70: 3)
  - Citizens' Committee of Inquiry [re assassination of John F. Kennedy]. Circulars, flyers, press releases, and clippings, 1964-1965 (Folder 70: 4)
  - Citizens' Committee on Relief [New York City]. Letters from persons seeking relief assistance, and notes, 1933 (Folder 70: 5)
  - Citizens' Committee to Free Earl Browder. Printed appeal and list of Cleveland branch officers, 1942 (Folder 70: 6)
  - Citizens Committee to Preserve American Freedoms. Correspondence, internal reports, flyers, circulated documents, informant's reports, and HUAC memoranda, 1952-1959 (Folder 70: 7)
  - Citizens for Kennedy/Fulbright-1968 [re Robert F. Kennedy and J. William Fulbright]. Printed appeal, 1967 (Folder 70: 8)
  - Citizens for Peace [Los Angeles]. Flyers, brochure, list of members, and clipping, 1973 (Folder 70: 9)
  - Citizens for Peace in Vietnam [Detroit]. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 70: 10)
  - Citizens for Victory. Articles of incorporation, statement, leaflets, and newsletter, 1943 (Folder 70: 11)
  - Citizens of Conscience of Washington Heights and Inwood [New York City]. Circular letters, leaflets, and flyers, 1966 (Folder 70: 12)
  - Citizens to Aid G.E. Strikers. Circular letter, 1970 (Folder 70: 13)
  - Citizens United to Abolish the Wood-Rankin Committee [HUAC]. Printed appeals, 1946 (Folder 70: 14)
  - City-Wide Tenants Council [New York City]. Circular letter and proposed bill, 1939 (Folder 70: 15)
  - Civil liberties (General) (Folder 70)
    - General. Correspondence, memoranda, speeches and statements by U.S. government officials, testimony of John T. Elliff re Federal Bureau of Investigation, Congressional speeches, and clippings, 1940-1973 (Folder 70: 16)
    - Issuances of miscellaneous organizations regarding civil liberties, prisoners, and miscellaneous individual defense cases. Flyers, leaflets, circular letters, lists, petitions, and serial issues, 1940-1973 (Folder 70: 17-18)
  - Civil Liberties Defense Fund. Letter, circulars, and appeals, 1968-1971 (Folder 71: 1)
  - Civil Rights Congress. Correspondence, circulars, flyers, leaflets, petitions, pamphlets (America's "Thought Police"; Argument to the Jury of Richard Gladstein in the New York Communist Trial; Red Tape and Barbed Wire), and clippings, 1947-1956 (Folder 71: 2)
  - Clark, Pieter Romayn. Printed article, 1966 (Folder 71: 3)
  - Class Struggle League. Circular letters and serial issues (Class Struggle), 1973 (Folder 71: 4)
  - Clergy and Laity Concerned [originally Clergy and Laymen Concerned about Vietnam] (Folder 71)
    - Clergy and Laity Concerned issuances. Press releases, printed appeals, circular letters, flyers, leaflets, and newsletters (Folder 71)
      - 1966-1967 (Folder 71: 5)
      - 1968 (Folder 71: 6)
      - 1969 (Folder 71: 7)
      - 1970 (Folder 71: 8)
      - 1971 (Folder 71: 9)
      - 1972 (Folder 71: 10)
      - 1973-1974 and undated (Folder 71: 11)
    - American Report. Serial issues (Folder 72)
      - 1970-1971 (Folder 72: 1)
      - 1972-1974 (Folder 72: 2)
    - Material about Clergy and Laity Concerned. Letter, clippings, and HISC memorandum, 1967-1974 (Folder 72: 3)
  - Clergymen's Emergency Committee for Vietnam. Printed appeal, 1966 (Folder 72: 4)
  - Cleveland Area Peace Action Council. Internal documents, lists of sponsors, circular letters, flyers, leaflets, and clippings, 1969-1970 (Folder 72: 5)
  - Cleveland Committee to End the War in Vietnam. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 72: 6)
  - Coalition for a Democratic Alternative [re Eugene J. McCarthy]. Flyer and printed appeals, 1968 (Folder 72: 7)
  - Coalition for an Anti-Imperialist March [New York City]. Printed appeals, 1968 (Folder 72: 8)
  - Coalition for an Anti-Imperialist Movement. Flyers, 1969 (Folder 72: 9)
  - Coalition for Economic Survival. Flyers and circulated documents, 1973 (Folder 72: 10)
  - Coalition for Jobs and Economic Justice. Internal document, list of supporters, and HISC memorandum, 1973 (Folder 72: 11)
  - Coalition on National Priorities and Military Policy. Circulated documents, flyers, list of member organizations, and testimony of Joseph S. Clark and Ronald Steel, 1969-1972 (Folder 72: 12)
  - Coffin, William Sloane. Clipping, 1967 (Folder 73: 1)
  - Columbia Independent Committee on Vietnam [Columbia University]. Newsletter and flyer, 1965 (Folder 73: 2)
  - Columbia Law Students [Columbia University]. Printed appeal, 1965 (Folder 73: 3)
  - Columbia Owl [Columbia University student newspaper]. Serial issues, 1962 (Folder 73: 4)
  - Columbia University antiwar protests. Printed appeals, serial issues, and clippings, 1964-1968 (Folder 73: 5)
  - Columbus Committee to Defend the Bill of Rights [Columbus, Ohio]. Circular letter, 1965 (Folder 73: 6)
  - Committee against Academic Repression [City University of New York]. Flyers, 1969 (Folder 73: 7)
  - Committee for a Boycott against Japanese Aggression. Clipping, 1938 (Folder 73: 8)
  - Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy (Folder 73)
    - Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy issuances. Circular letters, flyers, petitions, pamphlet (Facts on the Korean Crisis), and serial issues (Far East Spotlight; Spotlight on the Far East), 1947-1950 (Folder 73: 9)
    - HUAC report about the Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy with exhibit items, 1948 (Folder 73: 10)
  - Committee for a Democratic Spain. Letters, brochure, and flyers, 1962-1965 (Folder 73: 11)
  - Committee for a Peoples' Constitution [re Illinois state constitution]. Circular letter and press release, 1969 (Folder 73: 12)
  - Committee for Absolute Revolution [evangelical Christian organization]. Flyers, 1969 (Folder 73: 13)
  - Committee for Defense against Terrorist Attacks [Northern Illinois University]. Circulated document, 1970 (Folder 73: 14)
  - Committee for Democratic Election Laws. Leaflets, press releases, and circular letters, 1971-1972 (Folder 73: 15)
  - Committee for Direct Action [Madison, Wisconsin]. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 73: 16)
  - Committee for Draft Resistance [San Francisco]. Leaflet, list of endorsers, and clipping, 1967-1968 (Folder 73: 17)
  - Committee for Fifth Avenue Vietnam Peace Parade [New York City]. Letters, leaflets, internal documents, list of contacts, and informant's report, 1965-1966 (Folder 73: 18)
  - Committee for Foreign Policy Alternatives [Washington, D.C.]. Flyer, 1965 (Folder 73: 19)
  - Committee for GI Rights. Press releases, flyers, pamphlets (The GI's Handbook on Military Injustice; Kangaroo Court-Martial; Soldiers against the War), and clippings, 1967-1969 (Folder 73: 20)
  - Committee for Independent Political Action. Leaflet, flyers and clippings, 1965-1966 (Folder 73: 21)
  - Committee for Independent Political Action on the West Side [New York City]. Flyer and clipping, 1965-1966 (Folder 73: 22)
  - Committee for Informed Young Americans [re draft; Washington, D.C.]. Flyer, 1968 (Folder 73: 23)
  - Committee for Jews of Poland. Circular letter and pamphlet (The End of a Thousand Years), 1971 (Folder 73: 24)
  - Committee for Nonviolent Action. Letter by A. J. Muste, circulated letters and documents, flyers, leaflets, bulletins, and clippings, 1960-1972 (Folder 74: 1)
  - Committee for Peace and Freedom [Brooklyn]. Bulletin, 1964 (Folder 74: 2)
  - Committee for Peace Organization [Brooklyn]. Bulletins, 1961-1964 (Folder 74: 3)
  - Committee for Public Justice [American Civil Liberties Union affiliate]. Statement in Congressional hearing re Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1973 (Folder 74: 4)
  - Committee for Puerto Rican Political Prisoners [New York City]. Flyer, undated (Folder 74: 5)
  - Committee for Social Responsibility in Engineering. Serial issue (Spark), 1971 (Folder 74: 6)
  - Committee for Special Medical Aid to Cuba. Circular, 1965 (Folder 74: 7)
  - Committee for the First Amendment. Printed appeal and clippings, 1947 (Folder 74: 8)
  - Committee for the Formation of the New Party. Petition, clippings, and journal article, 1968 (Folder 74: 9)
  - Committee for the Fund for Milton Cohen vs. House Un-American Activities Committee. Letters, flyer, legal brief (Stamler and Hall vs. Willis et al.), and pamphlet (Dialogue on the Constitutionality of the Committee on Un-American Activities of the House of Representatives), 1965-1968 (Folder 74: 10)
  - Committee for the Presidio 27 [re GI dissidents]. Press release, flyers, and circulated letters and documents, 1969-1970 (Folder 74: 11)
  - Committee for the Restoration of Democratic Government in Greece. Printed appeal, 1967 (Folder 74: 12)
  - Committee for the Women's Peace March [New York City]. Flyer, undated (Folder 74: 13)
  - Committee for Theodore Pearson for Con-Con Delegate [re Illinois Constitutional Convention]. Circular letter, flyer, petition, and clipping, 1969 (Folder 74: 14)
  - Committee of Kent State Massacre Witnesses. Circular letter, 1970 (Folder 74: 15)
  - Committee of One Thousand [re abolition of HUAC]. Letters, press releases, flyers, and clippings, 1948-1949 (Folder 74: 16)
  - Committee of Outraged Parents [New York City]. Flyer, undated (Folder 74: 17)
  - Committee of parents of students at the University of Chicago. Clipping, 1969 (Folder 74: 18)
  - Committee of Responsibility [re Vietnamese war victims]. Circulars, flyers, leaflets, printed appeals, and clippings, 1967-1971 (Folder 74: 19)
  - Committee of Returned Volunteers [former Peace Corps members]. Flyers, leaflets, bulletins, circulated documents, and clippings, 1968-1970 (Folder 74: 20)
  - Committee of the Planning Professions to End the War in Vietnam. Printed appeals and clipping, 1967 (Folder 74: 21)
  - Committee of the Professions to End the War in Vietnam. Printed appeals, circular letters, flyers, and clippings, 1965-1968 (Folder 74: 22)
  - Committee on Conversation [re Vietnam War; Atlanta]. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 74: 23)
  - Committee on Latin American Solidarity [Los Angeles]. Flyer, 1969 (Folder 74: 24)
  - Committee to Aid American War Objectors [Canadian organization]. Circulars and flyers, 1967 (Folder 75: 1)
  - Committee to Aid the Bloomington Students [Indiana University]. Letter, circulars, and flyers, 1963-1968 (Folder 75: 2)
  - Committee to Aid the Monroe Defendants [black defendants in Monroe, North Carolina]. Letter, circulars, and newsletter, 1961-1965 (Folder 75: 3)
  - Committee to Aid the Vietnamese [Ann Arbor, Michigan]. Clippings, 1965 (Folder 75: 4)
  - Committee to Defend America by Keeping Out of War. Circulars, 1940 (Folder 75: 5)
  - Committee to Defend Resistance to Ghetto Life [New York City]. Printed appeals, circulars, and HUAC report, 1964-1967 (Folder 75: 6)
  - Committee to Defend the Conspiracy [re Chicago 8]. Printed appeals, circulars, and journal articles, 1969 (Folder 75: 7)
  - Committee to Defend the Panther 21. Circular letter, 1970 (Folder 75: 8)
  - Committee to Defend the Rights of Pfc. Howard Petrick. Press releases, statements, circulars, and pamphlet (Free Speech for Gis), 1967-1968 (Folder 75: 9)
  - Committee to Defend the Victims of the Committee on Un-American Activities. Pamphlet (In Defense of Human Rights), 1950 (Folder 75: 10)
  - Committee to End Sedition Laws. Letter and circulars, 1954-1955 (Folder 75: 11)
  - Committee to End the War in Vietnam [Los Angeles]. Circular letter, undated (Folder 75: 12)
  - Committee to Free Morton Sobell. Letter by Helen Sobell, circulars, and clippings, 1966-1968 (Folder 75: 13)
  - Committee to Impeach L.B.J. [Lyndon B. Johnson; Mill Valley, California]. Flyer, 1965 (Folder 75: 14)
  - Committee to Oppose the Deportation of Joseph Johnson [Minneapolis]. Letter, circulated documents, and flyers, 1966 (Folder 75: 15)
  - Committee to Secure Justice for Morton Sobell. Letter, circulated appeals, leaflets, flyers, pamphlet (The Case of Morton Sobell), printed articles, and clippings, 1956-1966 (Folder 75: 16)
  - Committee to Stop the War in Vietnam [University of Hawaii]. Clipping and HUAC note, 1965 (Folder 75: 17)
  - Committee to Support Middle East Liberation. Letter, circulars, flyers, newsletters, and pamphlet (An Israeli Worker's Answer), 1968-1970 (Folder 75: 18)
  - Common Cause. Press releases, circulars, and flyers, 1971 (Folder 75: 19)
  - Commonwealth College. Correspondence, and report on Commonwealth College by the Lutheran Research Society, 1946 (Folder 75: 20)
  - Communism (General). Material about communism (Folder 76)
    - Typescripts. "Talmudism and Communist Communications," 1962; "Communist Propaganda Artifices," undated (Folder 76: 1)
    - Problems of Communism. Serial issues, 1967 (Folder 76: 2)
    - World Strength of the Communist Party Organizations (U.S. Department of State Bureau of Intelligence and Research annual reports) (Folder 76)
      - 1968-1969 (Folder 76: 3)
      - 1970-1971 (Folder 76: 4)
    - Miscellaneous printed matter. Journal articles, clippings, "Chart of the World Revolution" (including Freemasonry and Illuminati), and pamphlets (Peace or Peaceful Coexistence?; Communism: Threat to Freedom), 1939-1974 (Folder 76: 5)
  - Communist Information Bureau. For a Lasting Peace, for a People's Democracy! Serial issues (Folder 77)
    - 1947 (Folder 77: 1)
    - 1948 (Folder 77: 2-4)
    - 1949 (Folder 78: 1)
    - 1950 and 1952 (Folder 78: 2)
  - Communist International (Folder 78)
    - Communist International. Serial issues (Folder 78)
      - 1924-1925 (Folder 78: 3)
      - 1931-1932 (Folder 78: 4)
    - Pamphlets (Program of the Communist International; Theses and Decisions of the 13th Plenum of the E.C.C.I.; The Twenty-One Conditions of Admission into the Communist International; We Are Fighting for a Soviet Germany), 1934-1936 (Folder 78: 5)
    - Printed excerpts from reports, resolutions and theses of Congresses of the Communist International, 1920-1935 (Folder 78: 6)
  - Communist Organizing Committee (Marxist-Leninist) [Baltimore]. Flyers, 1966 (Folder 78: 7)
  - Communist Party of Britain (Marxist-Leninist). Serial issue (Worker), 1970 (Folder 78: 8)
  - Communist Party, U.S.A. (Folder 79)
    - Papers of Jack Stachel, Communist Party leader, 1928-1929. (Folder 79: 1)
      Includes letters to Stachel from Charles Dirba, Jay Lovestone, Clarence Miller and others; Communist Party minutes and resolutions; and notes
    - Correspondence. Mainly circular letters and letters to subscribers to Communist Party publications (Daily World; People's World; Political Affairs) (Folder 79)
      - 1935-1969 (Folder 79: 2)
      - 1970-1974 (Folder 79: 3)
    - Communist Party, U.S.A. internal documents. Resolutions, reports, and miscellany, 1936-1972. (Folder 79: 4)
      Includes report by Henry Winston to 1950 national convention
    - Communist Party, U.S.A. internal educational materials. Educational bulletins, outlines, and syllabi, 1948-1973. (Folder 79: 5)
      Includes "Campaign against the Frameup of the Communist Leaders"; "Study Course on the Communist Party, the Working Class and Industrial Concentration"; "The Revolutionary Process in Latin America"
    - Communist Party, U.S.A. internal bulletins (Folder 79)
      - General (miscellaneous titles), 1938-1969 (Folder 79: 6)
      - Party Affairs (Folder 80)
        - 1966-1967 (Folder 80: 1)
        - 1970 (Folder 80: 2)
        - 1971 (Folder 80: 3)
        - 1972 (Folder 80: 4)
        - 1973 (Folder 80: 5)
        - 1974 (Folder 80: 6)
    - Communist Party, U.S.A. conference materials on Negro work, 1946-1948 (Folder 80: 7)
    - Communist Party, U.S.A. documentary summary of trial of Communist Party leaders ("Facts on the Trial of the 12"), 1949 (Folder 80: 8)
    - Daily Worker style manual, undated (Folder 80: 9)
    - People's World mailing list, 1961 (Folder 81: 1)
    - Communist Party, U.S.A. Longview, Washington, branch. Correspondence of Longview city officials with and about the local Communist Party branch re parade permits, etc., and related leaflets, internal documents, and clippings, 1932-1938 (Folder 81: 2)
    - Communist Party, U.S.A. election campaign literature and petitions, 1940-1973 (Folder 81: 3)
    - Communist Party, U.S.A. public issuances. Leaflets, flyers, local bulletins, and miscellany, 1934-1975 (Folder 81: 4)
    - Communist Party, U.S.A. press printed articles (Daily People's World; Daily Worker; Daily World; People's World; Worker) (Folder 81)
      - 1925-1926 (Folder 81: 5)
      - 1928 (Folder 81: 6)
      - 1929 (Folder 82: 1)
      - 1930-1938 (Folder 82: 2)
      - 1940-1943 (Folder 82: 3)
      - 1944-1946 (Folder 82: 4)
      - 1947 (Folder 82: 5)
      - 1948 (Folder 82: 6)
      - 1949-1951 (Folder 82: 7)
      - 1952 (Folder 83: 1)
      - 1953-1954 (Folder 83: 2)
      - 1955-1974 (Folder 83: 3)
    - Communist Party, U.S.A. serial issues (Folder 83)
      - Communist (Folder 83)